export const data = [
  {
    question: "What command is used to manage different NodeJS veresions?",
    option1: "nvm",
    option2: "npm",
    option3: "node",
    option4: "jsx",
    ans: 2,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which of the following routes is considered a RESTful configuration for ExpressJS?",
    option1: "/{id}",
    option2: "/:id",
    option3: "/?id=val",
    option4: "/id=val",
    ans: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "Collection is a group of MongoDB ___________?",
    option1: "Collection",
    option2: "Database",
    option3: "Table",
    option4: "Row",
    ans: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "BSON is a binary representation of .............. documents?",
    option1: "XML",
    option2: "JScript",
    option3: "all mentioned",
    option4: "JSON",
    ans: 4,
  },
  {
    question: "React component can return how many html tags",
    option1: "Two",
    option2: "Multiple",
    option3: "Single",
    option4: "Three",
    ans: 3,
  },
  {
    question: "What is Mongoose?",
    option1: "An object document mapping",
    option2: "An object document mapping",
    option3: "A small terrestrial carnivorous",
    option4: "None of the above",
    ans: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "ReactJs cover -------?",
    option1: "User Interface layer in an application",
    option2: "Data layer in an application",
    option3: "Both A and B",
    option4: "None of the Above",
    ans: 1,
  },
  {
    question:
      "What global variable is used to access the environment variables of a NodeJS application?",
    option1: "env",
    option2: "ENV",
    option3: "process.env",
    option4: "Process.getEnv()",
    ans: 3,
  },
  {
    question: "What is the definition of an Algorithm?",
    option1: "A set of instructions to perform a process",
    option2: "The answer to a question.",
    option3: "A question to be answered",
    option4: "A list of instructions.",
    ans: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "What is the key word used for when code is repeated or looped?",
    option1: "Instantaneous",
    option2: "Isolation",
    option3: "ISO File",
    option4: "Iteration",
    ans: 4,
  },
];
